ussoccerstore.com 2004-06-07

# Privacy Policy

| | 

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

 **The US Soccer Store is committed to protecting your privacy.** We use the information we collect about you to facilitate commercial transactions and to provide you with a more personalized shopping experience. We have created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of all of our customers and visitors. The following **Privacy Statement** discloses the information-gathering and dissemination practices and policies of the US Soccer Store and its ussoccerstore.com web site. **Privacy Policy Contents**  
Our Policy on Children  
Kinds Of Information We Collect From Our Users  
How We Use the Information We Collect  
Disclosure of Your Information  
Changing Your Personal Information  
Third Party Disclosures by You  
Our Security  
Contacting the U.S. Soccer Store

****
  1. **Our Policy On Children.**  
We do not encourage children to participate in providing us with any personally identifiable information. We ask that children (12 years of age and under) do not submit any personal information to us. If you are a minor under the age of 13 years, please use our services only under the approval and supervision of your parents or legal guardian(s). We support the guidelines and regulatory requirements provided in the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act [(COPPA)](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/index.html). ****
  2. **Kinds of Information We Collect From Our Customers.**  
The personally identifiable information we collect is used to facilitate delivery of products and/or services to our customers. In the process of providing these products and/or services, we require our customers to provide certain personally identifiable information. Specific details regarding the kinds of personally identifiable information we collect follows: ****
    1. **In the case of contests, promotions, and/or newsletter registrations:** We require all users and/or customers wishing to participate in any of our contests, drawings, sweepstakes, promotions, or newsletters to complete a Participant Registration Form. During this registration process we generate and collect certain personally identifiable information. **The personally identifiable information collected from our customers in completion of a registration form:** Customer's first name, last name, city, country, and email address. Winners of contests, drawings, sweepstakes, and/or promotions will be required to provide additional personally identifiable information such as a shipping address and telephone number.
 ****
    2.  **In the case of product and/or service purchases:**  
In order to complete the purchase of a product and/or service, an online credit card transaction is required. During this process we generate and collect certain verifiable personally identifiable information. **The personally identifiable information collected from our customers in completion of a product and/or service purchase:**   
The verifiable personally identifiable information required includes the customer's first and last name, first and last name of the credit card owner, credit card billing address, credit card number, credit card expiration date, customer's shipping address, phone number, and email address. The personally identifiable information we collect during this process is not stored onto our server unless the credit card charge transaction is successfully completed. In any event, the credit card information collected is deleted from our servers 30 days after a purchase.

**If a customer sends us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.**

****
  3. **How We Use the Information We Collect.**  
We internally use personally identifiable information about our customers to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site's content and layout. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and provide better service to our customers.

We may occasionally use a customer's email address and, in rare situations mailing address or phone number, to contact a customer regarding administrative matters or notices.

We may use information in the file we maintain about a customer to resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems.

****
  4. **Disclosure of Your Information.**  
We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about our customers to any third party. We do aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify a customer.

We cooperate with all law enforcement inquiries. We will disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials when required to do so in order to comply with a court order or to cooperate with law enforcement officials in the conduct of a criminal investigation.

****
  5. **Removing Your Personal Information.**   
Customers always have the option of removing their contact information from our database if they decide they no longer wish to receive future communications or to participate in any other part of our service. To do so, simply send email to:

****
  6. **Third Party Disclosures by You.**  
Our policy only addresses the use and disclosure of the personally identifiable information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your personally identifiable information to other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy customs and policies. Since we do not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personally identifiable information to others. ****
  7. **Our Security.**   
We use industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. However, please keep in mind that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet and/or the World Wide Web.
****
  8. **Contacting Us**   
If you have any questions about this privacy policy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact: Customer Service  
US Soccer Store  
P.O. Box 5218  
Granbury, Texas 76049

[customerservice@ussoccerstore.com  
](mailto:customerservice@ussoccerstore%20.com)  
Tel: 817-279-6349  
Fax: 817-573-8309
